// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Select correct lowercase letter 'A' ",
    answer: "a",
    options: [
      "b",
      "a",
      "c",
      "r"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Select correct lowercase letter 'G' ",
    answer: "g",
    options: [
      "k",
      "h",
      "s",
      "g"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Select correct lowercase letter 'Y' ",
    answer: "y",
    options: [
      "v",
      "y",
      "r",
      "a"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Select correct lowercase letter 'Q' ",
    answer: "q",
    options: [
      "s",
      "l",
      "q",
      "h"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Select correct lowercase letter 'J' ",
    answer: "j",
    options: [
      "i",
      "s",
      "v",
      "j"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Select correct lowercase letter 'D' ",
    answer: "d",
    options: [
      "z",
      "b",
      "d",
      "t"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Select correct lowercase letter 'N' ",
    answer: "n",
    options: [
      "m",
      "n",
      "x",
      "k"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Select correct lowercase letter 'R' ",
    answer: "r",
    options: [
      "v",
      "R",
      "r",
      "a"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Select correct lowercase letter 'H' ",
    answer: "h",
    options: [
      "a",
      "y",
      "c",
      "h"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Select correct lowercase letter 'V' ",
    answer: "v",
    options: [
      "v",
      "x",
      "a",
      "u"
    ]
  }
  
];
